

GEERTHIKA LAKSHMANAN

UI/UX Designer www.geerthika.com

P: +91 9095232109, +91 8248272742
Tamilnadu 630301, India
argeerthi14@gmail.com
LinkedIn

EDUCATION

2022

UI/UX Design, Designboat Bootcamp, Bangalore, India

2015-2020

B.Arch, Department of Architecture, Anna University, Chennai, India

SKILLS

Software	Design
Figma	Design System
Sketch	User flow
Invision	Web/Mobile Design
SketchUp 3D	Wireframing
Adobe XD	UI Design
Adobe Photoshop	Prototype
Adobe Illustrator	Visual Design
Adobe Indesign	Marketing Design

Programming

HTML CSS

Bootstrap JavaScript

LANGUAGES

English, Tamil, Hindi

ABOUT

A blend of UI/UX and Architecture. With 2+ years of experience in design field, I love working at the intersection of creativity and User Centered Design. My expertise has been in Wireframe, Prototyping, Sitemap, Product Design, App Design, Web Design, User Interface Design, User Research, Concept Design, HTML5, CSS3.

EXPERIENCE

User Expereince Designer (June 2022 - Aug 2022)

Redd Experience Design, Bangalore - B2C Worked on the crypto web projects, prepared moodboards for DEX of Persistence One. In charge of Persistence One's marketing collateral deliverables, including the pitch deck, BNB Deck, and PStake. Prepared design mood boards and final products, UI interface, research and study. I contributed to the task of redesigning the marketing collaterals for the brand Persistence One, which is a Dubai-based company.

UI UX Designer (June 2021 - April 2022)

Freelance Designer B2B - Worked on UI products, with design system, user flow, competitive analysis, research, wireframe, prototype and branding. Collaboration with startsups in Design Branding, Logo, Event Posters, Concept art, Colour theory, Social media management. (Collaboration: Lacasa Studio, Kanoji Design studio, Design Partners, Chui Huay Lim Teochew Cusine, Singapore, Black Architects)

Junior Designer (Jan 2020 - Oct 2021)

HCP design Planning & Management pvt.ltd, Ahmedabad - Worked on the project of 'Central Vista Redevelopment of India, Delhi'. Involved in Indian government presentation deliverables.

Internship (June 2018 - March 2019)

SR+A Architects, Mumbai - Architecture Internship